Association of Canadian Publishers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Committee meetings, papers and files, 1971 - 1984; F-57-4; 2.37 m of textual records
  - Education, 1973 - 1983; F-57-4-9; 71 cm of textual records
    - Canadian Content - Agendas, Minutes and Papers, Educational and Library Materials Work Group, Toronto Board of Education (Cotter Report), 1975 - 1976; F-57-4-9-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-11)
    - Canadian Content - (as above, also clippings, draft Cotter Report), 1976 - 1977; F-57-4-9-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-11)
    - Canadian Content - (clippings, Hansards, article, correpondence from Rowland Lorimer), 1976 - 1979; F-57-4-9-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-11)
    - Canadian Content, 1975 - 1977; F-57-4-9-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Canadian Learning Materials Centre, 1979 - 1980; F-57-4-9-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Canadian Learning Materials Centre, 1981 - 1982; F-57-4-9-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Canadian Materials Resources - (Survey of Provincial Education Ministries), 1976; F-57-4-9-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Canadian Studies Foundation, 1978 - 1980; F-57-4-9-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Commision on Declining Enrollment in Ontario, 1977 - 1978; F-57-4-9-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Council of Maritime Premiers, 1980; F-57-4-9-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Council of Ministers of Education, 1977 - 1982; F-57-4-9-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Curriculum (Teaching Canada for 80's), 1979; F-57-4-9-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Education Handbook - A Basic Handbook for the Canadian Educational Market (drafts, correspondence), 1979 - 1980; F-57-4-9-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - English EL-Hi Report in Canada, 1979 - 1981; F-57-4-9-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Learning Materials Development, 1979 - 1981; F-57-4-9-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Market Statistics, 1976 - 1979; F-57-4-9-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-12)
    - Publishing Policy, 1973 - 1979; F-57-4-9-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Publishing Policy Brief, 1977 - 1978; F-57-4-9-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Publishing Policy Brief, 1978 - 1979; F-57-4-9-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Publishing Policy, 1976 - 1977; F-57-4-9-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Robinson Study - Where Our Survival Lies, 1978 - 1979; F-57-4-9-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Seneca Workshop, 1979; F-57-4-9-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Stanley House Conference - Resources for Canadian Education, 1977 - 1978; F-57-4-9-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Textbook Campaign - Association of American Publishers, 1977 - 1978; F-57-4-9-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Textbook Expenditures - correspondence, worksheets, (Provincial, by Publishers), 1974 - 1975; F-57-4-9-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Provinces - Alberta, 1979 - 1982; F-57-4-9-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Provinces - Alberta Curriculum Department / Publishers Conferences, 1976 - 1980; F-57-4-9-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Provinces - British Columbia, 1975 - 1981; F-57-4-9-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-13)
    - Provinces - Manitoba, 1977 - 1979; F-57-4-9-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - New Brunswick, 1978; F-57-4-9-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - Newfoundland, 1977 - 1980; F-57-4-9-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - Nova Scotia, 1977 - 1982; F-57-4-9-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - Ontario, Ministry of, 1975 - 1983; F-57-4-9-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - Ontario Circular #14, 1975 - 1982; F-57-4-9-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - Ontario Curriculum, 1977 - 1979; F-57-4-9-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - Ontario School Boards, 1980 - 1982; F-57-4-9-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - Ontario Learning Materials Development Plan Committee, 1975 - 1976; F-57-4-9-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - Ontario Learning Materials Development Plan Committee, 1975 - 1976; F-57-4-9-0-54 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - Ontario Learning Materials Development Plan Committee, 1976 - 1977; F-57-4-9-0-55 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - Ontario Learning Materials Development Plan Committee, 1977 - 1978; F-57-4-9-0-56 (Archival box - standard 57-14)
    - Provinces - Ontario Learning Materials Development Plan Committee, 1979 - 1980; F-57-4-9-0-57 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
    - Provinces - Ontario Learning Materials Development Plan Committee, 1981 - 1982; F-57-4-9-0-58 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
    - Provinces - Ontario French Language Fund, 1977 - 1982; F-57-4-9-0-59 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
    - Provinces - Prince Edward Island, 1975 - 1979; F-57-4-9-0-60 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
    - Provinces - Saskatchewan, 1981; F-57-4-9-0-61 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
    - Computers - Communications Systems and Publishing Conference, Toronto, 1981; F-57-4-9-0-62 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
    - Computers - Database Consortium Feasibility Study, B. Beardsley, 1981; F-57-4-9-0-63 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
    - Educational Computers, Functional Specifications, Canadian Advancement Technical Association, 1981; F-57-4-9-0-64 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
  - Finance, 1979 - 1982; F-57-4-10; 2 cm of textual records
    - Finance - Minutes and Papers, 1979 - 1981; F-57-4-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
    - Finance - Subcommittee, 1979 - 1982; F-57-4-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
  - Government Action, 1971 - 1972; F-57-4-11; 1 cm of textual records
    - Government Action - Agendas, Minutes and Papers, 1971 - 1972; F-57-4-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
  - Government Relations, 1977 - 1979; F-57-4-12; 5 cm of textual records
    - Government Relations - Correspondence, 1977 - 1978; F-57-4-12-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-15)
    - Government Relations - Papers, 1978; F-57-4-12-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-16)
    - Government Relations - Agendas, Minutes and Papers, 1978 - 1979; F-57-4-12-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-16)
    - Government Relations - Papers, 1978 - 1979; F-57-4-12-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-16)
  - Library Relations, 1973 - 1978; F-57-4-13; 6 cm of textual records
    - Library Relations - Minutes and Papers, 1973 - 1977; F-57-4-13-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-16)
    - Library Relations - Minutes and Papers, 1977; F-57-4-13-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-16)
    - Library Relations - Minutes and Papers, 1975 - 1977; F-57-4-13-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-16)
    - Library Relations - Minutes and Papers, 1977 - 1978; F-57-4-13-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-16)
  - Management, 1975 - 1981; F-57-4-14; 16 cm of textual records
    - Executive Sub-Committee - Agendas, Minutes and Papers, 1975 - 1976; F-57-4-14-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-16)
    - Management Committee - Papers, Agenda, Minutes and Papers, 1976; F-57-4-14-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-16)
    - Agenda, Minutes and Papers, 1976; F-57-4-14-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-17)
    - Agenda and Papers, 1976 - 1977; F-57-4-14-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-17)
    - Agenda, Minutes and Papers, 1977; F-57-4-14-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-17)
    - Papers, 1977 - 1978; F-57-4-14-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-17)
    - Minutes and Papers, 1978; F-57-4-14-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-17)
    - Agenda, Minutes and Papers, 1979 - 1980; F-57-4-14-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-17)
    - Papers, 1980 - 1981; F-57-4-14-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-17)
    - Management - Agenda, Minutes and Papers, 1981; F-57-4-14-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
  - Media, 1973 - 1981; F-57-4-15; 1 cm of textual records
    - Media (Relations Or Liaison) - Agenda, Minutes and Papers, 1973 - 1981; F-57-4-15-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
  - Membership, 1972 - 1984; F-57-4-16; 45 cm of textual records
    - Membership, 1972 - 1974; F-57-4-16-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
    - Membership - Applications, 1974; F-57-4-16-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
    - Membership - Applications, 1974 - 1976; F-57-4-16-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
    - Membership - Member Data Sheets, 1975 - 1976; F-57-4-16-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
    - Membership - Fees and Assessments, 1976 - 1979; F-57-4-16-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
    - Membership - Rejected Applications, 1977 - 1980; F-57-4-16-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
    - Membership - Supporting, 1974 - 1978; F-57-4-16-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
    - Membership - Papers, 1974 - 1980; F-57-4-16-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
    - Membership - Correspondence, 1979; F-57-4-16-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
    - Membership - Correspondence, 1980; F-57-4-16-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-18)
    - Membership - Correspondence and Papers, 1980; F-57-4-16-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Applications, 1980; F-57-4-16-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Member Data Sheets, 1980 - 1981; F-57-4-16-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Papers, 1981; F-57-4-16-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Minutes and Papers, 1980 - 1982; F-57-4-16-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Member Data Sheets, 1981 - 1982; F-57-4-16-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Member Data Sheets, 1982 - 1983; F-57-4-16-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Alcuin Books, 1976 - 1978; F-57-4-16-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Alive Books, 1980 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Alive Press, 1977; F-57-4-16-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - All About Us/Nous Autres, 1975 - 1978; F-57-4-16-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Ander-Bo Books, 1973 - 1974; F-57-4-16-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Anson, 1977; F-57-4-16-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - ARC Publications, 1978 - 1981; F-57-4-16-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Avondale Press, 1973; F-57-4-16-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Backdoor Press, 1980 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Ballantrae Foundation, 1972 - 1975; F-57-4-16-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Berandol Music Ltd., 1975 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Bio-management and Research, 1975 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Black Fish, 1980 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Blewointment Press, 1975 - 1979; F-57-4-16-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Borealis Press Ltd., 1976 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Boston Mills Press, 1975 - 1983; F-57-4-16-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Brunswick Press, 1976 - 1978; F-57-4-16-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Burns and MacEachern, 1975 - 1978; F-57-4-16-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
      Notes
    - Membership - Campbell's Publishing, 1979; F-57-4-16-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Canadian Music Sales, 1977; F-57-4-16-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Canadian Stage and Arts, 1974 - 1975; F-57-4-16-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Canadian Theatre Review, 1978 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-19)
    - Membership - Charases Press, 1973 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Cherry Publishers, 1979; F-57-4-16-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Clare, William, 1973 - 1976; F-57-4-16-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Coles Publishing Co., 1977 - 1978; F-57-4-16-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Commcept Publishing, 1977 - 1981; F-57-4-16-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Commoners' Publishing, 1976 - 1980; F-57-4-16-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Consolidated Amethyst Communications, Inc, 1979 - 1983; F-57-4-16-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Content Publishing, 1975 - 1976; F-57-4-16-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Cove Press (Danzek Books), 1974 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Credit Management Services, 1979 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Culturama, 1979 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Curriculum Division, Department of Education, N.W.T., 1973 - 1976; F-57-4-16-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Delta Canada, 1976; F-57-4-16-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Deluge Press, 1979 - 1983; F-57-4-16-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Discovery Press, 1974 - 1980; F-57-4-16-0-54 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Dorset Publishing, 1978 - 1979; F-57-4-16-0-55 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Dumont Press, 1976 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-56 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Les Edition du Bleu, 1980; F-57-4-16-0-57 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Elgin Publications, 1979 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-58 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Fforbez Enterprises, 1974 - 1983; F-57-4-16-0-59 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Fireweed Press, 1977; F-57-4-16-0-60 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Fireweed, 1981 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-61 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Gray's Publishing, 1976 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-62 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Greentree Publishing, 1974 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-63 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Guernica Editions, 1981 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-64 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Hancock House, 1975 - 1980; F-57-4-16-0-65 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Harris, Frederick, 1976; F-57-4-16-0-66 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Hosford Publishing, 1981 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-67 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Intermedia Press, 1974 - 1978; F-57-4-16-0-68 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - International Self-Counsel Press, 1975 - 1978; F-57-4-16-0-69 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Jarman Publications, 1975 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-70 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Kakabeka Publishing, 1974 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-71 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Khoisan Artists, 1978; F-57-4-16-0-72 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Ladysmith Press, 1975; F-57-4-16-0-73 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Leslie Music Supply, 1977; F-57-4-16-0-74 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Lighthouse (Atlantic Institute of Education), 1978 - 1980; F-57-4-16-0-75 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - London Free Press, 1974 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-76 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Lyndeview Publications, 1974 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-77 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - MacKenzie's Books, 1978 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-78 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - MacMillan Co. of Canada, 1976 - 1980; F-57-4-16-0-79 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - McNab Circle, 1975 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-80 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Metromap Publications, 1975 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-81 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Milestone Publications, 1979; F-57-4-16-0-82 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - Nairn Publishing House, 1974 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-83 (Archival box - standard 57-20)
    - Membership - New Brunswick Museum, 1979; F-57-4-16-0-84 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - New Canada Press, 1975 - 1983; F-57-4-16-0-85 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - New Hogtown Press, 1976 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-86 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Nor-Rand Publishing, 1974 - 1975; F-57-4-16-0-87 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Otter Press, 1974 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-88 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Paideia Press, 1979 - 1980; F-57-4-16-0-89 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Pandora Publishing, 1975 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-90 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Peguis Publishers, 1980 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-91 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Peter Martin Associates, 1975 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-92 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Petheric Press, 1978 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-93 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Potlatch Publications, 1978 - 1983; F-57-4-16-0-94 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Prairie Publishing, 1979 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-95 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Press Collective, 1975; F-57-4-16-0-96 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Research Institute of Northern Canada, 1976; F-57-4-16-0-97 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Rhino Books, 1979 - 1983; F-57-4-16-0-98 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - M.F. Rousseau, 1973 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-99 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Saltaire Publishing, 1974 - 1975; F-57-4-16-0-100 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Samuel to Stevens, 1975 - 1983; F-57-4-16-0-101 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - H.M. Simpson, 1976; F-57-4-16-0-102 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Slavuta Publishers, 1977; F-57-4-16-0-103 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Soft Press, 1981 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-104 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Square Deal Publications, 1973 - 1979; F-57-4-16-0-105 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Stagecoach Publishing, 1979 - 1981; F-57-4-16-0-106 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Summerthought Ltd., 1977 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-107 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Tad Publishing, 1974 - 1975; F-57-4-16-0-108 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - T.M.C. Publishing, 1975 - 1977; F-57-4-16-0-109 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Tecumseh Press Ltd., 1975 - 1984; F-57-4-16-0-110 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Gordon V. Thompson Ltd., 1975 - 1976; F-57-4-16-0-111 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Tundra Books, 1975; F-57-4-16-0-112 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Virgo Press, 1980 - 1982; F-57-4-16-0-113 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Waterloo Music Co., 1975 - 1976; F-57-4-16-0-114 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Waxwing Productions, 1976 - 1978; F-57-4-16-0-115 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Membership - Wooden Anchor Press, 1978; F-57-4-16-0-116 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
  - Nominating, 1977 - 1980; F-57-4-17
    - Nominating - Papers, 1977 - 1980; F-57-4-17-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
  - Ontario Publishers, 1977 - 1983; F-57-4-18; 1 cm of textual records
    - Minutes and Papers, 1977 - 1979; F-57-4-18-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Agenda, Minutes and Papers, 1980 - 1982; F-57-4-18-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Papers, 1978 - 1980; F-57-4-18-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
    - Minutes and Papers, 1981 - 1983; F-57-4-18-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-21)
  - Paperbacks, 1972 - 1974; F-57-4-19; 1 cm of textual records
    - Papers and Correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-57-4-19-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
  - Priorities, 1977 - 1979; F-57-4-20; 1 cm of textual records
    - Minutes and Papers, 1977 - 1979; F-57-4-20-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
  - Production, 1978 - 1982; F-57-4-21; 18 cm of textual records
    - Minutes and Papers, 1978 - 1979; F-57-4-21-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
    - Agenda, Minutes and Papers, 1980; F-57-4-21-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
    - Minutes and Papers, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
    - Study Proposal, A Study into the Current State and Future OPTIONS of Book Production in Canada, by Evelyn Ross, 1980 - 1982; F-57-4-21-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
    - Study Draft, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
    - Study Final Report, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
    - Study Papers: Western, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
    - Study Papers: Winnipeg, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
    - Study Papers: Saskatoon, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
    - Study Papers: Edmonton, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
    - Study Papers: B.C., 1981; F-57-4-21-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-22)
    - Study Papers: Atlantic, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-23)
    - Study Papers, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-23)
    - Study Papers: Directory Material, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-23)
    - Study Papers: Ontario, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-23)
    - Study Papers: Quebec, 1981; F-57-4-21-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-23)
  - Public Information, 1976 - 1980; F-57-4-22; 3 cm of textual records
    - Minutes and Papers, 1976 - 1980; F-57-4-22-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-23)
    - Papers, 1977 - 1978; F-57-4-22-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-23)
  - Search, 1980; F-57-4-23; 1 cm of textual records
    - Papers, 1980; F-57-4-23-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-23)
  - Trade Relations, 1975 - 1982; F-57-4-24; 15 cm of textual records
    - Minutes and Papers, 1976; F-57-4-24-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-23)
    - Papers, 1975 - 1977; F-57-4-24-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-23)
    - Minutes and Papers, 1977; F-57-4-24-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Papers, 1977; F-57-4-24-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Minutes and Papers, 1977 - 1978; F-57-4-24-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Papers, 1978; F-57-4-24-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Papers, 1978; F-57-4-24-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Papers, 1978; F-57-4-24-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Papers, 1978; F-57-4-24-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Minutes and Papers, 1978 - 1979; F-57-4-24-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association, 1979; F-57-4-24-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Correspondence, 1979 - 1980; F-57-4-24-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Display Boxes, 1979; F-57-4-24-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Fairs and Export, 1978 - 1979; F-57-4-24-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Agendas, Minutes and Papers, 1980; F-57-4-24-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Correspondence, 1980; F-57-4-24-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association, 1980; F-57-4-24-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
    - Agendas, Minutes and Papers, 1981 - 1982; F-57-4-24-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-24)
- Subject files, 1951 - 1984; F-57-5; 4.91 m of textual records ca. 50 photographs; Physical description: 1 photograph located in F-57-5-1-3 Physical description: 26 photographs located in F-57-5-9-11